Guide to the Zdenek Nemeck Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1934-69; Series V; 0.25; (1 box)
  - Papers, miscellaneous, 1957, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 914)
  - Papers, political, [1939-45?] (Box 28, Folder 915)
  - Printed material, 1956-69
    - Ceskoslovensky zahranicní ústav v exilu: Studie, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 916)
    - The Guild reporter v. XXIV, no. 16, 1957 Aug 9 (Box 28, Folder 916)
    - The New Leader, v. XL, no. 34, 1957 Aug 26 (Box 28, Folder 916)
    - Svet práce, no. 3/69, 1969 Jan 22 (Box 28, Folder 916)
  - Publicity, [1956], n.d. (Box 28, Folder 917)
  - Research notes (Z. N.), n.d. (Box 28, Folder 918)
  - Thank-you note, [1941] (Box 28, Folder 919)
- Oversize, [1946]
  - "Evropská kantiléna": 20 pages galley proofs and proofs of 36 illustrations, and 1 cover, [1946] (Box 29, Folder 920)
  - "Le secret des Nations Unies," Le Patriote, 1960 Dec 18 (Box 29, Folder 920a)
  - Rataje nad Sázavou. Místní národní vybor...usnesl...jmenovati... Zdenka Nemecka...cestnym obcanem (description inside box), 1948 Jan (Box 30, Folder 921)
  - Magazine illustration of "Hrazené Rataje," 1 sheet, [early 1900] (Box 30, Folder 922)